A Guide to the Constituent Correspondence of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1993.
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Governor's Office, 1993., Extent: 11 cubic feet (11 boxes). (Box 14-24)
  - Virginia - Bottoms v. Bottoms Ruling (5 of 8), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Virginia - Bottoms v. Bottoms Ruling (6 of 8), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Virginia - Bottoms v. Bottoms Ruling (7 of 8), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Virginia - Bottoms v. Bottoms Ruling (8 of 8), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Liaison Office (1 of 5), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Liaison Office (2 of 5), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Liaison Office (3 of 5), 1993. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Liaison Office (4 of 5), 1993. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Liaison Office (5 of 5), 1993. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Virginia State Bar, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Worker's Compensation, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Welcome Letters, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Series III. Scheduling Office, 1993 Jan-Mar., Extent: 1 cubic foot (1 box). (Box 24)
  Scheduling Office correspondence, 1993, is housed in 1 box and is arranged chronologically. This series includes invitations to attend and requests for appearances by Governor Wilder at various events, as well as attached letter of regret. These Scheduling Office records arrived with this transfer of Constituent Correspondence. For additional Scheduling Office records see Records of the Scheduling Office of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1989-1994 (Accession 35539, 34185).
  - Scheduling Office - Invitations/Requests and Regrets, 1993 Jan. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Scheduling Office - Invitations/Requests and Regrets, 1993 Jan. (Box 24, Folder 7a)
  - Scheduling Office - Invitations/Requests and Regrets, 1993 Jan. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Scheduling Office - Invitations/Requests and Regrets, 1993 Feb. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Scheduling Office - Invitations/Requests and Regrets, 1993 Feb. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Scheduling Office - Invitations/Requests and Regrets, 1993 Feb. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Scheduling Office - Invitations/Requests and Regrets, 1993 Mar. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Scheduling Office - Invitations/Requests and Regrets, 1993 Mar. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Scheduling Office - Invitations/Requests and Regrets, 1993 Mar. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Scheduling Office - Invitations/Requests and Regrets, 1993 Mar. (Box 24, Folder 15)